world backup day yes that's the Saturday
세계 백업 하루 예 , 토요일입니다.
can you believe it's here upon us
그것이 우리에게 여기에 있다고 믿을 수 있습니까 ?
already March 31st every year is the
이미 매년 3 월 31 일이
year that we geeks celebrate your need
우리 괴짜가 너의 필요를 축하하는 해.
to back up perhaps there should be like
아마도 거기에 있어야 백업 처럼
backup day a month but world backup day
한 달에 한 번 백업 하지만 세계 백업 날짜로
once you personally should have backup
한번 개인적으로 백업해야합니다.
day once a week maybe but definitely a
일주일에 한 번 어쩌면 틀림 없이
day to remind you it's like you've got
너 에게 생각 나게 해줄거야.
to change the batteries in your fire
당신의 화재로 배터리를 변경
detector your smoke alarms right exactly
당신의 연기 감지기를 정확하게 탐지하십시오
site detector you do that when you the
사이트 탐지기 를 사용하면
clock goes forward and back right right
시계가 앞으로 나아가고 오른쪽으로 돌아 간다.
yes I also flip the mattress of my life
네 , 제 인생 의 매트리스 도 뒤집 습니다.
in my bedroom there you go you do that
내 침실에 거기 가서 너 그렇게 해.
so you change the alarm batteries we
그래서 우리는 알람 배터리를 변경합니다.
flip the mattress I've got a pillow top
매트리스를 뒤집어 라 베개 탑이있다.
so I'm stuck I'll rotate it how's that
그래서 나는 꼼짝 못하게 될거야.
okay yeah perfect and and we're also
좋아 , 완벽 하고 우리는 또한
going to make sure our backups are
우리의 백업이 있는지 확인하는 것
working exactly don't just backup twice
정확히 두 번만 백업 하는 것이 아닙니다.
a year
1 년
but make sure twice a year that your
하지만 일년에 두 번 확인 귀하를
back is working I moved everything off
다시 일하고있다. 나는 모든 것을 옮겼다.
of my laptop onto a USB flash drive that
내 노트북을 USB 플래시 드라이브 에
is my backup and that is very common now
내 백업 이며 지금 은 매우 일반적입니다.
some of you or say oh are you focusing
너 중 일부는 말하고, 아 , 너 집중하고있어?
on me here because I'm you know that I
내가 너 때문에 내가 여기에있어.
did that I know a lot of folks who have
내가 가진 많은 사람들을 알고 있었나요?
done that okay so it's our
그것은 그래서 그 좋아 일을 우리
responsibility to educate you as to what
무엇에 관해서 당신 을 교육 할 책임
a real backup is okay so a couple of
진짜 백업은 괜찮습니다.
things that we need to think about how
우리가 어떻게 생각 해야하는지
you're backing up how often you're
당신은 얼마나 자주 당신을 백업하고 있어요.
backing up how many copies of your files
파일의 얼마나 많은 복사본을 백업
exist what's going to happen if say the
말하면 무슨 일이 벌어 질지
worst happens your house burns down
집안이 불타고 최악의 상황이 발생합니다.
right and all your computers are
오른쪽 및 모든 컴퓨터가 있습니다.
destroyed what's gonna happen here data
여기에 무슨 일이 일어날 지 파괴 된 데이터
and what is going to be lost or also
어떤 또한 분실하거나 할 것입니다
here's something that a lot of people
사람들이 여기 뭔가가있어 그 많은
don't think about Sasha mm-hmm what is
사샤에 대해 생각하지 마세요. mm-hmm 무엇입니까?
the process going to be like if I ever
가는 과정은 만약 내가 지금까지처럼되고
have to restore from my backup good
내 백업에서 복원해야합니다.
question and there is a very good
질문은 매우 좋다.
question because a lot even companies
질문이 많아서
will have exceptional backup systems in
탁월한 백업 시스템을
place and then not have the security to
장소를 찾은 다음 보안이 없다.
protect them against ransomware then
그때 그들을 ransomware 로부터 보호하라.
ransomware hits and they're down for
ransomware 히트와 그들이 내려 간다 .
weeks right and thousands upon thousands
수주월에 수천, 수천
of dollars in IT hours
IT 시간당 달러
and so we've got to take that approach
그래서 우리는 그 접근법을 취해야합니다.
okay so first of all how are you backing
좋아, 그럼 우선 어떻게 지지하고 있니?
up
쪽으로
can I ask you personally can I ask you
개인적으로 물어봐도 될까요?
can it be a rhetorical question is it
그것은 수사학적인 질문 일 수 있는가?
weird that I don't I assumed that okay
나는 그 괜찮 가정하지 않는 것이 이상한
okay so where where is your data that's
좋아요. 그럼 어디서 데이터를 볼 수 있을까요?
maybe that's the first question here's
어쩌면 그 첫 번째 질문은 여기입니다
the thing okay this is going to sound
좋아, 이게 들릴거야.
hoarse is not a good start this is not a
쉰 목소리는 좋은 시작이 아니다.
good sir okay I know the importance of I
좋은 선생님 , 저는 저의 중요성 을 압니다.
know the importance of backing up but I
백업 의 중요성 을 알고 있지만
also know who I am and how I survive in
내가 누구인지 , 어떻게 살아남을지
this world isn't generally on your
이 세상 은 일반적 으로 당신에게 달렸 습니다.
intelligence and capability okay so
지성과 능력이 그렇게 좋았어.
every week I'm gonna say sash I have you
매주 나는 너에게 새시가 있다고 말할 거야.
backed up this week where is your data
이번 주 에 귀하의 데이터가 백업되었습니다.
think about that where are where are the
그곳에 대해 생각해보십시오 .
things that mean the most to you I have
내가 가진 가장 중요한 것을 의미하는 것들
I think Google where Google now is it
나는 구글이 지금 어디 있는지 구글 이라고 생각 한다.
your phone my phone does a backup thing
내 전화기는 백업 일을한다.
it does a backup thing let's go to the
그것은 백업 작업을 수행하자.
last question which is how onerous is it
마지막 질문은 얼마나 까다 롭다.
to get the files back should you have a
당신이해야 파일을 다시 얻을
crash just these are some of these are
충돌 만이 이들 중 일부는있다
rhetorical questions just so that it
수사적 질문만으로
makes you think I where is your data it
내 데이터가 어디 있는지 생각하게 해.
is on my on Dave's computer okay yes and
Dave의 컴퓨터에 있습니다.
on my phone the same data some of the
내 휴대폰에서 동일한 데이터의 일부를
same data some of okay not I don't okay
괜찮의 일부 동일한 데이터가 없습니다 내가 좋아하지 않습니다
so he backs up he backs up some very
그래서 그는 매우 백업 백업
important files this is he's better at
중요한 파일 이 더 좋습니다.
this than I am sure okay but he backs up
이게 내가 확신하는 것보다 낫지 만 그가 백업 해.
to an external hard drive but it's also
외장형 하드 드라이브로
still in the apartment okay so that
아파트에 아직도 괜찮아.
takes us to what if there was a fire
불이났다 면 우리 를 어떻게 생각 하느냐 ?
where is your data right it is in the
데이터 권리가 어디에 그것은이다
same place same physical location as the
동일한 장소와 동일한 물리적 위치
original files now if we were in the
지금 우리가에 있다면 원본 파일
apartment at the time of the fire then
화재시 아파트 다음
but but say say we were at least the
하지만 우리가 적어도
external hard drive is easy to get right
외장형 하드 드라이브는 쉽게 얻을 수 있습니다.
but but we are we probably weren't there
그러나 우리는 아마 거기에 없었습니다.
because definitely not it that fire was
확실히 화재가 아니기 때문에
not our fault so we were not there
우리 잘못 이 아니 어서 우리가 거기 에 없었다.
no after setting the fire you ran that's
네가 쏘는 불을 지킨 후에는 안된다.
right yeah we couldn't take anything
우린 아무것도 못 가져갈 수있어.
I would never burn my place so this is a
나는 결코 나의 장소를 태우지 않을 것이다. 그래서 이것은 a이다.
question that you have to ask yourself
네가 스스로에게 묻어야 할 질문
and and that is a horrible scenario that
그리고 그것은 끔찍한 시나리오입니다.
we we do not hope on any of you but it's
우리는 당신에게 희망이 없지만
a good reality check for us to say okay
우리가 알기에 좋은 현실 확인
where would my data be if this happened
이 경우 내 데이터는 어디에 있습니까?
if the worst happened what's my option
최악의 일 이 내 선택권 인 경우
it's more about it's not where should
더 중요한 것은 어디에서해야하지 않느냐입니다.
your data be or what you know what
귀하의 데이터는 귀하가 알고있는 것 또는 귀하가 알고있는 것입니다.
services should I subscribe to or what
서비스 를 구독해야합니까?
software should I use it's more let's
소프트웨어를 사용해야할까요?
get into the mindset of understanding
이해 의 사고 방식 에 빠지다.
how a backup actually works so a backup
백업이 실제로 작동하는 방법 그래서 백업
is never a backup unless there are
가없는 한 백업 결코
multiple copies of the files that mean
의미 하는 여러 파일 사본
something to you so if for example
당신에게 뭔가 예를 들어, 만약 그렇다면
you've taken a bunch of photos and
너는 많은 사진을 찍었고
videos with your phone all your family
휴대 전화로 가족 과 함께하는 모든 동영상
pictures and everything are on your
사진 과 모든 것이 당신의 사진 에 있습니다.
phone and then you transfer them on to
전화 로 전송 한 다음에 전송할 수 있습니다.
your laptop because you want to back
노트북 당신은 백업 할 때문에
them up right but then they're on your
그들을 오른쪽으로 올려라. 그러나 그들은 당신 위에있다.
laptop and not your phone that's not a
노트북이 아니고 휴대 전화 가 아닌
backup it's not bad okay if they're on
백업 그들이에 있다면 괜찮 나쁘지 않아
your computer and then you transfer them
귀하의 컴퓨터를 누른 다음 그들을 전송
to an external hard drive and now
외장형 하드 드라이브에 연결하고 지금
they're only on the external hard drive
외장형 하드 드라이브 에만 있습니다.
that's not a backup similarly if you do
당신이 그렇게한다면 그것은 백업이 아닙니다.
have two copies you've got one on the
두 장의 복사본이 있습니다 .
laptop and one on your external hard
노트북 과 외장 하드 에 하나씩
drive but the external hard drive is
외장형 하드 드라이브는
plugged into that laptop 24/7 and
해당 노트북에 24 시간 연중 무휴로 연결 하고
sitting on the desk next to it also not
또한 옆에있는 책상에 앉아 있지
a back not a backup I can answer I know
백업이 아니라 내가 대답 할 수있는 것을 안다.
what is not a backup yeah more times
네 번 이상 백업 것이 아니다
than not people move things off of their
사람들이 물건 을 자신의 물건에서 벗어나는 것보다
computers to free space you'll buy an
당신이 살 공간 을 확보 할 수있는 컴퓨터
external hard drive or something you'll
외장형 하드 드라이브 또는
transfer all the files on to it never
모든 파일을 절대로 전송하지 마라.
thinking that this is now the lone copy
이것이 지금은 혼자 라고 생각합니다.
and it's a drive that could easily be
그리고 그것은 쉽게 될 수있는 드라이브입니다.
tripped over it could easily be dropped
그 위에 걸려 넘어 지면 쉽게 떨어질 수있다.
and if it has spinning if it's a
그리고 만약 그것이 회전한다면
spinning drive like a terabyte or two
1 테라 바이트 또는 2 열 드라이브
terabyte or three terabyte drive is
테라 바이트 또는 3 테라 바이트 드라이브는
gonna be a spinning drive it's not a
회전하는 드라이브가 될거야.
solid-state drive so when you move it
솔리드 스테이트 드라이브 로 이동할 때
you can feel that centrifugal force as
그 원심력을 다음과 같이 느낄 수 있습니다.
you move it have you ever had that
너는 그것을 가지고 있다.
feeling where if you pick up a moving
당신 이 움직이는 곳을
heart on hard drive it's moving mm-hmm
하드 드라이브에 심장이 움직입니다. mm-hmm
so that's a spinning hard drive and if
그래서 그것은 회전하는 하드 드라이브이고 if
that ever got bumped while it's spinning
회전하는 동안 부딪 혔어.
if it ever got dropped while it's
그것이 떨어지는 동안
spinning you are going to be hard
당신은 열심히 될 것입니다 회전
pressed to get the data off of that
그 떨어져 데이터를 얻을 누르면
drive because it's moving at 7,200
7,200으로 움직이기 때문에 운전 하십시오.
rotations per minute and there's a
분당 회전 수 와
little teeny-weeny needle that's
작은 바늘 바늘이야.
floating on an air cushion just above
방금 위에 공기 방석에 뜨는
the platter right okay and there are
플래터는 괜찮아.
actually several of these little needles
사실 몇 개의 작은 바늘
and they use magnetic sensors in order
자기 센서를 순서대로 사용합니다.
to read and write the
읽기 및 쓰기
from the hard drive flash and if they
하드 드라이브 플래시에서 그들이 경우
touch if they so much as just touch that
너무 많이 만지면 만져주세요.
drive 7200 rotations per minute think
분당 7200 회전을 생각하십시오.
about that how fast that is if it just
그것에 대해 그게 만약 단지를 얼마나 빨리
touches it's not going to just touch and
만지기 만하면 안된다.
then pop back and keep going hunky-dory
그 다음에 다시 튀어 나와 계속 늠름한 - dory
no right it's gonna edge a big circle
아니 , 큰 원을 그리게 될거야.
right into the platter surface of that
그 오른쪽의 플래터 표면에
hard drive I picture this like somebody
하드 드라이브 나는 이것을 누군가처럼 묘사 한다.
walking with like two full cups of
두 잔의 컵 처럼 걷다.
coffee right and trying not to spill
커피를 엎 지르지 않고 엎 지르지 않으려 고
those coffees like that's hard enough
그 커피는 충분히 힘들어.
right do you know okay this is your data
맞아,이게 당신의 데이터인지 알지?
so fake so we have to have multiple
그래서 가짜 그래서 우리는 여러 개 있어야합니다.
copies I'd recommend that you always
복사본을 항상 권하고 싶습니다.
have an off-site copy
오프 사이트 사본이있다.
now if off-site like through the
이제 오프 사이트와 같은 경우
internet is not an option for you
인터넷은 선택 사항 이 아닙니다.
because that can be pricey you've got to
그게 값이 비쌀 수 있기 때문에
have storage and you've got to have the
저장 공간이 있어야하고
bandwidth in order to do it you can
대역폭을 확보하기 위해
simply go get a consumer hard drive yeah
단순히 소비자 하드 드라이브를 가져 가라.
an external hard drive copy the files to
외부 하드 드라이브 가 파일 을
that hard drive and put it in a safety
그 하드 드라이브와 안전에 넣어
deposit box or take it to work and put
예금 상자에 넣거나 일하고 집어 넣으십시오.
it in your desk drawer and do that every
책상 서랍에 넣고 그걸 할 때마다
single week or month depending on how
방법에 따라 1 주 또는 1 개월
much information you want to lose should
많은 정보 를 잃어 버리고 싶습니다.
the worst ever happen always have at
최악 의 상황은 항상 발생합니다.
least two copies maybe three of
적어도 두 권 은
everything that matters to you okay
너에게 중요한 모든 것은 괜찮아.
buy two of those drives and then you can
드라이브 두 대를 사면 다음과 같이 할 수 있습니다.
just swap them back and forth and take
그냥 앞뒤로 바꿔서 가져 가세요.
one off-site and leave the other one at
하나는 오프 사이트로 남겨두고 다른 하나는
home that's what you need to do mm-hmm
집에서해야 할 일은 바로 mm-hmm입니다.
any other quick questions for me as we
나를위한 다른 빠른 질문들
move on I want to see next week you're
다음 주에 너보고 싶어.
gonna say I backed up everything that I
거 내가 모든 것을 백업 말하는 그 I
have I feel like yeah yes another common
나는 네처럼 느껴져. 예. 또 다른 공통점.
just a commonplace thing USB flash
그냥 평범한 물건 USB 플래시
drives plugged into a computer moving
드라이브가 컴퓨터에 연결됨
the files on to it they get broken
그것들에 대한 파일 들이 깨졌습니다.
somebody trips over the computer drops
누군가가 컴퓨터 방울을 통해 여행하다.
the laptop and breaks the USB port and
노트북과 USB 포트 및
that happens more often than you want to
당신이 원하는 것보다 더 자주 일어나는 일
think so definitely you know just make
그렇게 생각하면 틀림없이 알게 될 것입니다.
sure there are multiple copies okay that
확실히 여러 복사본 이 있습니다.
is key I want to hear from you I want
내가 원하는 걸 듣고 싶다.
you to comment below let us know how
당신이 아래 에 코멘트 하는 방법을 우리에게 알려주 는 방법
you're backing up what is your solution
당신은 당신의 솔루션이 무엇인지를 백업하고 있습니다.
to this problem mm-hmm and what would
이 문제에 대해 mm-hmm
happen if where your data is was to burn
당신의 데이터가 어디서 태워지면 일어난다.
down right that's what we want to ask
아래로 우리가 물어보고 싶은 것입니다.
ourselves that's what we want to know
우리 자신이 그것이 우리 가 알고 싶은 것입니다.
and if this just quick little chat has
이 간단한 채팅에
helped you to realize that hey maybe
어쩌면 그걸 깨달을 수 있었을거야.
I've got a
나는
something different about my backups and
내 백업 및 대해 다른 뭔가
you actually take action please comment
실제로 행동을 취 하십시오.
below comment on our website comment on
우리 웹 사이트에 대한 의견 아래에 코멘트
our YouTube channel let us know what
YouTube 채널에서 무엇을 알 수 있습니까?
what it is that you put into action and
당신 이 행동 하게 한 것은 무엇입니까?
how you're backing up and if you have
백업하는 방법과 보유하고있는 경우
any questions or need advice just let us
어떤 질문이나 조언이 필요 하시면 저희에게 알려주십시오.
know I'll probably do what you're doing
니가하고있는 일을 아마 할거라는 걸 알아.
[Music]
[음악]
[Applause]
[박수 갈채]